Good morning.
Whoa, the wind is strong today.
No joke, not to mention it's freezing out here.
It feels like fall. Did you hear?
Huh? Hear what?
I guess it's the season for warm drinks now.
Looks like autumn has finally arrived.
As seasons must change, I'm feeling left behind again.
There she is! Hanabi!
I'm sorry, but you were absent when we were picking roles for the school festival.
Hey, I hope you don't mind just being a stagehand, Hanabi.
Uh, stage? What do I need to do?
Oh, don't worry. Just leave the heavy lifting to the band club and you'll be fine.
Mm-hmm.
You only have to do the easy work, like watching over the schedule and stuff. Please?
Hanabi, that's why you should go meet with them.
Alright, I'll do it.
That's awesome! Now everyone has a job!
Thank you, Hanabi!
Wow, that's already cold.
Mookie.
Mookie...
The wedding is coming up. They're having it over spring break.
Brother came by. He thought it would be best if I heard it from him.
Huh?
Hana?
Congratulations.
We talked a bit. On our way home.
Poor Mugi.
I guess it didn't work out. Serves him right, though.
Are you surprised it's so sudden?
No, I'm not surprised at all.
Really? Why not?
Because it was really obvious to me. I knew you were in love with her.
So what's this? You stopped wearing glasses.
Huh? Yeah. I broke my glasses. So I just...
She asked you to wear contacts, didn't she?
What? How did you know?
It's so obvious. But for the record, I preferred you in glasses.
Ugh.
Because...
The way he looks right now...
Reminds me of the days when he was just mine.
And...
It still kind of hurts.
Hana, will you come to the wedding?
Hana?
Yeah.
I'll be there.
Of course I will.
Thank you.
Right this way, please.
Would you like some cheese?
Okay. So this will be our final schedule for the rest of the festival day.
I'm sure you're all tired by now from all the prepping you've been doing.
But let's do it!
Dude, look at her. Her eyes are glazed over.
Wait, wasn't she the one who was all about building this stage in the first place?
You two over there! Students A and B!
If you're late at any point today, I'm throwing you in the bonfire!
Wow. I'm just glad things came together in the end.
Hey!
Oh, my date made it here.
So you're off with your boyfriend?
Try not to be late!
What's up? Do you not have time?
Yeah, I have plenty of time.
Although, I am a bit tired.
Did you need to go rest somewhere?
No.
Who do I really want to be with?
I locked away the few names that popped into my head, quietly shutting them down.
Where do you want to start?
Hey, let's eat something first!
Totally!
Looks like I've got time before they need me back at the stage.
Please come check us out!
We're doing a fashion show!
Why not come in and see?
We have lots of great outfits to show!
Hurry up or we'll miss it!
Bye!
That I've loved my precious Mookie much longer and more honestly than you could ever dream of.
I feel refreshed and alive now.
You'll understand once you bother doing something for your own well-being.
Thank you for attending the show!
Your dress was incredible, Miss Noriko.
Really?
The embroidery is so intricate.
Did you do it all yourself?
Yeah, amazing!
Do you always make all of your films together?
I do.
Really? I thought so.
I've been meaning to ask you a lot.
Hey, will you teach me how to make clothes, Noriko?
It's Moka!
What do I want?
I just don't know.
You're late, Yasuraoka!
Hurry up and help someone, will ya?
Where is this box going?
No, I'm gonna make it!
Left, right, quick, quick, quick!
Hurry up!
Yes, ma'am!
Hanabi, could you bring me the cord?
Uh, yes!
Sorry, Hanabi, can you help me with the flyers?
Uh, sure, okay!
Yasuraoka, take that equipment round to the back!
Which one?
That one!
Now hurry up!
Okay!
Sorry, excuse me.
Nobody's here.
I'm so tired.
It feels nice to be alone.
You can see things clearer when you're by yourself.
That's right.
I was alone to begin with.
How could I have forgotten that?
You scared of being alone?
Mm-hmm.
No.
Not anymore.
I was always alone.
Everyone's alone, really.
Then I guess this is meaningless, too.
Yeah, it is.
In the end.
Mm-hmm.
Why did we do it?
Why did we make that promise?
If it's all just meaningless?
Why?
I fell asleep.
It hurt my shoulder.
Why?
Why did we ever have to meet?
All right, volunteers, stay behind after the graduation ceremony.
Uh, what's with all this work just for us to celebrate our teacher's wedding?
It seems all a bit too much.
Lest you forget, you're part of the action committee, so stop talking.
Now make sure to return all the tools when you're done.
They go in the back.
What?
Again?
Hurry up and do it!
Yes, ma'am?
Hey, Hanabi.
Let me help you out there.
Uh, really?
Uh, thanks for that.
What's your...
I'm Moriyama.
We're in the same class.
Well, starting this year, at least.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Hanabi, you doing okay there?
Let's just put these away.
Yeah, sorry.
Thanks again, with helping me and all.
You saved me.
Uh, sure.
Listen, Hanabi.
Huh?
How have things been between you and Mugi?
It's just that I haven't seen the two of you around each other lately.
So, um, Hanabi, if you're interested, maybe you'd like to...
Well, um...
All right, that's enough from you.
Hanabi belongs only to me.
Now kindly back off of her, will ya?
W-what?
Let's go.
Uh...
Hmm.
I...
I'm sorry.
But...
It's appreciated very much.
Oh.
Hey, Sanai.
Don't worry.
I was just joking back there.
Why did you come and rescue me?
You still want your space?
If I'm not mistaken?
Yeah.
That's correct.
You're just the best.
Huh?
Why are you crying right now?
You're so nice.
You're always so nice, Sanai.
Okay, okay.
Just blow your nose already.
I...
I didn't think you would ever want to talk to me again.
Hmm.
I wouldn't do that to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry it took so long.
You cut your hair off.
Hmm.
You're the girl from the exam earlier.
Huh?
You didn't braid your hair today.
Uh...
Yeah, that was me.
You mind if I touch your hair?
Huh?
Wow.
Your hair is amazing.
It looks so pretty down.
At that very moment,
I felt forgiven for some reason.
It was like it was my first breath.
The world looked down and took me in.
And...
Sanai...
This hairstyle looks nice on you.
But anything would.
I don't know.
I feel so refreshed now.
It was nice of them to do this for us
Wasn't it? I'm so embarrassed
Here, we all signed a card for you
Oh wow, thank you so much
Hanabi, I heard you were invited to go to Mr. Kanai's wedding
Did I get that right?
Uh, yeah
I'm so jealous
I've never been invited to attend a real live wedding before
This will be my first one, too
Oh, that's the dream, isn't it?
Spending the rest of your life with the person you truly love
The dream?
It's the bouquet toss
What? It's the toss
Why are you not throwing the stupid thing?
Just take it
What are you doing to me?
Take it
Fine, are you happy now?
Miss Akane?
But next time
Don't let him get stolen
That's none of your concern anymore
It turns out
The promise we made
And the days we spent together
Had no meaning in the end
In the beginning
I was just lonely
I wanted to be touched
I ended up falling in love
With your warmth
Hanabi
The contract we made back then
Back when we were lonely
Does that matter?
Now that we've both lost our loves
So
Does that mean our contract is voided?
Or does it mean
We're able to make a new contract
One that fits us both
I'm sorry
Don't apologize, stupid
Just so you know
Akane changed
She really did
Yeah, yeah
Hey, it's true
Yeah, I know that
Well, after all
Brother did choose her in the end
I guess I was wrong about her
I love brother
Enough to accept his choice
With no question
I'm okay now
I can put it into words
Now that I know
Mugi
You did well
I'm really proud of you
You too
I felt for the first time
Since we've known each other
We avoided physical comfort
And used our words instead
To express our pain
We were never able to do
That sort of thing before
We talked a lot that day
About everything
Making up for our lost time
Oh man
What a long first love
So painful
They say your first love
Is never the one that comes true
Despite it being autumn
The sunlight feels warm
Shining through the dust
And settling in the still air around us
It smells like old wood grounding us in place
Where time is both everlasting and fleeting
I can take in the scene playing out
And quietly breathe in
Making a decision
I'm glad I met you Mugi
You really helped me out a lot
In the end
We're looking for real love
We know it's something deep
That can't easily be found
No matter how hard we pray for it
It may be something we'll never have
And who really knows
We may hurt worse next time
It could make us feel more isolated
More alone in the sea of despair
But
We'll continue to seek it
I don't want
To be apart
To have to let go of you once again
I want to hold you
I don't want things to end
Please don't let me go
I don't want it to end
But
Goodbye for now
We're good
We don't need to be saved just yet
We're going to look for real love this time around
That's why we'll continue
To live on
God?"
I don't want to
I don't want it to be back
I don't want it to be rempli
I don't want it to be
But
To live on
We're good
I don't want it
That's why we called it
And
Promised
I don't want it
Me
You can
You will
茶
That's why I love it
I'm glad
I want it
Community
I don't want it
I want it
to live on